Frances Wasserlein fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- MA Thesis records, 1895 - 1990; F-162-3; 82 cm of textual records 34 photographs: slides 22 sound recordings; Physical description: 34 photographs (slides) are located in file F-162-3-3-0-28.
  - General Research Materials, 1895 - 1990; F-162-3-3; 46 cm of textual records 85 periodicals 34 photographs: slides; General note: 34 photographs (slides) are located in file F-162-3-3-0-28; digital copies are available (stored on 2 CDs).
    - Vancouver Indochinese Women's Conference, April 1972, 1971 - 1987; F-162-3-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 162-5)
      Vancouver Indochinese Women's Conference; Textual records
    - Archives - Formation of a Women's Archives Society, 1986; F-162-3-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 162-5)
    - Women's Movement History, 1980; F-162-3-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 162-5)
    - Feminism and Abortion - media articles, 1980; F-162-3-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 162-5)
    - Marge Hollibaugh's Abortion Caravan Scrapbook, 1968 - 1970; F-162-3-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 162-5)
    - Slides - Abortion Caravan - Barbara Hicks, Photographer, April 1970 - May 1970; F-162-3-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 162-5)
      Hicks, Barbara; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Martine Lanctot - History of Women's Movement in Quebec, 1980; F-162-3-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 162-5)
      Martine Lanctot; Textual records
    - Publications: Collections of Feminist Writing - General, 1968 - 1970; F-162-3-3-0-30 (Archival box - standard 162-5)
    - Publications: Women's Rights Movement in British Columbia, 1976 - 1978; F-162-3-3-0-31 (Archival box - standard 162-5)
    - Publications: Vancouver Women's Health Collective, 1978; F-162-3-3-0-32 (Archival box - standard 162-5)
      Vancouver Women's Health Collective; Textual records
    - Publications: Women's Rights Movement in Canada, 1975 - 1986; F-162-3-3-0-33 (Archival box - standard 162-5)
    - Publications: Abortion and Birth Control Policy, 1982 - 1985; F-162-3-3-0-34 (Archival box - standard 162-5)
    - Publications: Recommendations of the Royal Commission on the Status of Women, 1990; F-162-3-3-0-35 (Archival box - standard 162-5)
      Royal Commission on the Status of Women in Canada; Textual records
    - Peak - Marcy Toms, 1968 - 1971; F-162-3-3-0-36 (Archival box - standard 162-5)
      Peak Publications Society; Marcy Toms; Textual records
    - The Pedestal, vol. 1, 1969 - 1974; F-162-3-3-0-37 (Newspaper box 162-10)
    - The Pedestal, vol. 2, 1969 - 1974; F-162-3-3-0-38 (Newspaper box 162-11)
  - Miscellaneous Papers and Publications, 1969 - 1988; F-162-3-4; 13 cm of textual records 3 sound recordings; Physical description: sub-series includes 5 audio cassettes (originals and copies).
    Sub-series consists of newspapers, publications from women's liberation organizations, academic papers, copies of the Vancouver Women's Caucus newspaper The Pedestal, recordings of CBC Morningside broadcasts, and a taped interview with Dr. Margaret Benston. Benston was a founding member of the Women's Studies Department at SFU and a prominent activist for social justice in Canada.
    Access to sound recordings is restricted for preservation reasons due to the age and fragility of the medium. Archives will provide access only through digitization of the originals. As of October 2012, no sound recordings have been digitized. Consult the reference archivist for more information about access these recordings.
    - CBC Morningside, 7 December 1987; F-162-3-4-0-0-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3601, Audio cassette OBJ-3602)
      Canadian Broadcasting Corporation; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-4-0-1 (orig.), F-162-item37, F-162-item38.
    - CBC Morningside, 1-2 February 1988; F-162-3-4-0-0-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-3639, Audio cassette OBJ-3640)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-4-0-3 (orig.), F-162-item39, F-162-item40.
    - Maggie Benston on Early Women's Movement at SFU, [198-?]; F-162-3-4-0-0-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-3641)
      Benston, Maggie; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-4-0-5 (orig.), F-162-item41.
    - PSA Papers, 1970 - 1979; F-162-3-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 162-6)
      Department of Political Science, Sociology and Anthropology; Textual records
    - Miscellaneous Publications 1/3, 1969 - 1979; F-162-3-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 162-6)
    - Miscellaneous Publications 2/3, 1969 - 1979; F-162-3-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 162-6)
    - Miscellaneous Publications 3/3, 1969 - 1979; F-162-3-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 162-6)
    - Publications - Women: A Journal of Liberation, 1969 - 1970; F-162-3-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 162-6)